Guide to the President's Office General Subject and Correspondence Files 1910-1974
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Oregon State College/University, 1910-1974; Series 2
  - Student Life
    - Living Groups (Reel-folder 13.06)
    - Living Organizations - Veterans Emergency Housing (Reel-folder 130.2262)
    - Living Groups - Dormitories - Men, 7/1/1947 and prior (Reel-folder 130.2270)
    - Student Relations - Stinner Hall - Other Clubs - Advisory - Other (Reel-folder 130.2271)
    - Living Groups (Reel-folder 13.07)
    - Students - Oregon State Mothers Club (Reel-folder 130.2278)
    - Mothers Club, 1942-1948 (Reel-folder 130.3379)
    - Prizes and Awards - Waldo Prizes (Reel-folder 130.2280)
    - Prizes and Awards - Waldo Prizes, 1937-1943 (Reel-folder 130.2281)
    - Prizes and Awards - Ingalls Award (Wallace) (Reel-folder 130.2283)
    - Students - Foreign Student Counselor, 1949-1960 (Reel-folder 130.2284)
    - Students - General, 1950-1958 (Reel-folder 130.2285)
    - Students - International House Center (former Alpha Gamma Rho Frat. House ) (Reel-folder 130.2286)
    - Students - Prospective, 1949-1957 (Reel-folder 130.2287)
    - Reference File - Student Life - Statistics - Race and Religion (Reel-folder 130.2289)
    - Senior Credo and Philosophy, 1950 (Reel-folder 130.2289a)
    - Veterans (Reel-folder 130.2290)
    - Veterans Rehabilitation Program (Reel-folder 13.08)
  - Administration - Campus Events
    - Annual Agricultural Staff Conference, 1951-1964 (Reel-folder 87.221)
    - Charter Day (OSU), 1966 (Reel-folder 87.222)
    - Charter Day, 1959-1965 (Reel-folder 87.223)
    - Centennial Awards - F. L. Ballard (OSU) (Reel-folder 87.224)
  - Wayne V. Burt (Reel-folder 87.225)
  - Ava Milam Clark (Reel-folder 87.226)
  - F.A. Gilfillan (Reel-folder 87.227)
  - Vernon Cheldelin (Reel-folder 87.228)
  - George Gleeson (Reel-folder 87.229)
  - E. R. Jackman (Reel-folder 87.230)
  - W. J. Kerr (Reel-folder 87.231)
  - E. B. Lemon (Reel-folder 87.232)
  - Clifford E. Maser (Reel-folder 87.233)
  - W. F. McCullough (Reel-folder 87.234)
  - Herman Oliver (Reel-folder 87.235)
  - Earl Price (Reel-folder 87.236)
  - Margaret Snell (Reel-folder 87.237)
  - A. L. Strand (Reel-folder 87.238)
  - Helen Gilkey (Reel-folder 87.239)
  - Milton Harris (Reel-folder 87.240)
  - U. G. Dubach (Reel-folder 87.241)
  - David T. Mason (Reel-folder 87.242)
  - Charles Sprague (Reel-folder 87.243)
  - Oregon Wheat Growers League (Reel-folder 87.244)
  - A.L. Strand (Reel-folder 87.245)
  - Angus L. Bohmer (Reel-folder 87.246)
  - Sun Choi (Reel-folder 87.247)
  - E. H. Wiegand (Reel-folder 87.248)
  - Roland E. Dimick (Reel-folder 87.249)
  - J. W. Forester (Reel-folder 87.250)
  - W. E. Milne (Reel-folder 87.251)
  - John C. Scharff (Reel-folder 87.252)
  - T. J. Starker (Reel-folder 87.253)
  - Kirby Bromfield (Reel-folder 87.254)
  - Distinguished Professor Award
    - J. E. Oldfield (1 of 2), 1966 (Reel-folder 87.255)
    - J. E. Oldfield (2 of 2), 1966 (Reel-folder 88.255)
    - E. N. Castle (Reel-folder 88.256)
  - Centennial Award - George W. Peavy (Reel-folder 88.257)
  - Centennial Award - Bernard Malamud (Reel-folder 88.258)
  - Centennial Award - Wayne Morse (Reel-folder 88.259)
  - OSC - Admin. - Camus Events - Beaver Boys State (Reel-folder 88.260)
  - Beaver Review (Reel-folder 88.260a)
  - Administration
    - Campus Events (Reel-folder 16.01)
    - Committees (Reel-folder 16.02)
    - Councils (Reel-folder 16.03)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 16.04)
  - Experiment Station
    - Forest Experiment Station - Forest Research Laboratory, 1964-1968 (Reel-folder 92.377)
    - General, 1961 (Reel-folder 92.378)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station
    - Leases, Loans (Reel-folder 92.379)
    - Research Oregon State Liquor Commission Agreement (Reel-folder 92.380)
    - Research Tennessee Valley Authority Project Agreement Ore.- 836.2 (Dr. Cheney) Contract TV-54722, Alfalfa on Aiken Soils (Reel-folder 92.381)
    - Agriculture Research Foundation, 1964-1965 (Reel-folder 92.381a)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station - Federal Extension Service - Mouse Control and Study - State Emergency Board - Appropriation (Reel-folder 92.382)
  - Federal Extension Service - Agricultural
    - Community Service and Continuing Education (Reel-folder 92.387a)
    - Proposed Agreement for a Parent Training Program to be Conducted by the Federal Cooperation Extension Service (Reel-folder 92.387b)
  - Research Centers and Institutes - Computer Center
    - Environmental Health Programs, 1968 (Reel-folder 93.393)
    - Genetics Institute, 1968 (Reel-folder 93.394)
    - Marine Science Laboratory (1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Reel-folder 93.395)
    - Marine Science Laboratory (2 of 3), 1963-1967 (Reel-folder 93.396)
    - Marine Science Laboratory (3 of 3), 1969-1970 (Reel-folder 93.397)
    - Nutrition Research Institute, 1968 (Reel-folder 93.398)
    - Radiation Center (1 of 3), 1966-1968 (Reel-folder 93.399)
    - Radiation Center (2 of 3), 1960-1966 (Reel-folder 93.400)
    - Radiation Center (3 of 3), 1968-1970 (Reel-folder 93.401)
    - Sea Grant Colleges, 1966-1968 (Reel-folder 93.402)
    - Water Resources Research Institute (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Reel-folder 93.403)
    - Water Resources Research Institute (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 93.404)
    - Forest Research Laboratory (Reel-folder 93.404a)
  - Institutional Services
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 21 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Business Office, 1968-1969 (Reel-folder 93.405)
    - Business Office - General, 1969-1970 (Reel-folder 93.406)
    - Fiscal Affairs - General (1 of 2), 1970 (Reel-folder 93.407)
    - Fiscal Affairs - General (2 of 2), 1971 (Reel-folder 93.408)
    - General (Reel-folder 21.01)
    - Personnel Coordinator - Admissions (1 of 3), 1967-1969 (Reel-folder 94.424)
    - Personnel Coordinator - Admissions (2 of 3), 1965-1967 (Reel-folder 94.425)
    - Personnel Coordinator - Admissions (3 of 3), 1963 (Reel-folder 94.426)
    - Registrar (Reel-folder 21.02)
    - Admissions - General, 1971 (Reel-folder 94.432)
  - Instruction
    - Divisions (Reel-folder 22.01)
    - Schools (Reel-folder 22.02)
  - Cooperative Managers Association Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Reel-folder 97.459a)
  - Instruction - Schools
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 23 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - Speech Department, 1960-1966 (Reel-folder 97.460)
    - Pharmacy, 1960 (Reel-folder 97.461)
    - Science (Reel-folder 23.01)
  - Physical Plant - Construction - Buildings
    - Bioscience (Microbiology, Fish and Game) (Reel-folder 98.466)
    - Administration Building (Reel-folder 98.467)
    - Administration Building (new), 1968 (Reel-folder 98.268)
  - NSF - Science Development Program (Stardust) (Reel-folder 98.469)
  - Physical Plant
    - Construction - Buildings (Reel-folder 25.01)
    - Buildings (Reel-folder 25.02)
    - Construction - Buildings (Reel-folder 25.03)
    - Departments (Reel-folder 25.04)
    - General (Reel-folder 25.05)
  - Student Life
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 26 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Alumni Association - Board of Directors, 1958 (Reel-folder 104.528)
    - Associated Students - General, 1961-1971 (Reel-folder 104.528a)
    - Associated Students - Senate - General (Reel-folder 104.528b)
    - Alumni Association - General (1 of 2), 1963-1966 (Reel-folder 104.529)
    - Alumni Association - General (2 of 2), 1963-1966 (Reel-folder 105.529)
    - Dean of Men - Discipline (1 of 2), 1959-1961 (Reel-folder 105.530)
    - Dean of Men - Discipline (2 of 2), 1961 (Reel-folder 105.531)
    - Dean of Women - Discipline (Reel-folder 105.532)
    - Educational Funds - Student Loan Fund, 1958-1968 (Reel-folder 105.533)
    - Educational Funds - General (Reel-folder 105.534)
    - Health Service, 1960-1964 (Reel-folder 105.535)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Reel-folder 26.01)
    - Living Groups (Reel-folder 26.02)
    - Mothers Club, 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 107.567)
    - Foreign Student Counselor, 1960 (Reel-folder 107.568)
    - General (1 of 2), 1958-1961 (Reel-folder 107.569)
    - General (2 of 2), 1961 (Reel-folder 107.570)
    - Students Prospective, 1957-1968 (Reel-folder 107.571)
  - Dean of Students (Reel-folder 107.572)
  - Status Item No. 3 - Non-Resident Students (Reel-folder 107.573)
  - Status Item No. 6 - Studies Abroad (Reel-folder 107.574)
  - Status Item No. 4 - Varsity Rifle Team (Reel-folder 107.575)
  - Committees - Commencement, 1972 (Reel-folder 136.01)
  - Institutional Services
    - General - Archivist (Reel-folder 136.02)
    - Fiscal Affairs - General (Reel-folder 136.03)
    - Department of Information (Reel-folder 136.04)
    - International Education (Reel-folder 136.05)
    - Memorial Union - Board of Directors (Reel-folder 136.06)
    - General - Memorial Union (Reel-folder 136.07)
    - General - Memorial Union - Dining Services (Reel-folder 136.08)
    - General - Motor Pool (Reel-folder 136.09)
    - General - Department of Printing (Reel-folder 136.10)
    - General - Publications Office (Reel-folder 137.11)
    - General - Publications - University Press (Reel-folder 137.12)
    - Civil Services - General - Collective Bargaining (Reel-folder 137.13)
    - Civil Services - Pay Rates - Wage Adjustment Effective (Reel-folder 137.14)
    - Civil Services - Classification (Reel-folder 137.15)
    - Civil Services - Personnel Actions (Reel-folder 137.16)
    - Civil Services - Procedures - General (Reel-folder 137.17)
    - Classified Personnel - General (Reel-folder 137.18)
  - Instruction
    - Schools (Reel-folder 28.01)
    - Divisions (Reel-folder 28.02)
    - Schools - Humanities and Social Sciences (Reel-folder 28.03)
    - Schools (Reel-folder 28.04)
  - Papadopoulas, Michael (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 140.92)
  - Papadopoulas, Michael (Reel-folder 141.92)
  - Instruction
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 29 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Schools (Reel-folder 29.01)
    - Divisions - Military Science - Army, 1967 (Reel-folder 141.111)
    - Schools (Reel-folder 29.02)
    - Services (Reel-folder 29.03)
  - Commencement (1 of 2), 1972 (Reel-folder 142.129)
  - Commencement (2 of 2), 1972 (Reel-folder 143.129)
  - Libraries and Museums
    - Library - General, 1969 (Reel-folder 143.130)
    - Museums - Braly Ornithological Collection (Reel-folder 143.131)
    - Museums - Herbarium (Reel-folder 143.132)
    - Museums - Horner Museum of the Oregon County (Reel-folder 143.133)
  - Physical Plant
    - Construction - Campus Model (Reel-folder 143.134)
    - Pre-Printing Submittal - NOT the Final Report (Reel-folder 143.135)
    - Pre-Printing Submittal - NOT the Final Report - Appendix A (Reel-folder 143.136)
    - Construction - Heating Plant (Electrical Distribution Facilities) - Utility Tunnel (Reel-folder 143.137)
    - Construction - Heating Plant - Utility Tunnel - Steam and Electrical Distribution lines - Complete Record (Reel-folder 143.138)
    - Construction - Heating Plant - Utility Tunnel (Reel-folder 143.139)
    - Construction - Heating Plant, 1968 (Reel-folder 143.140)
    - Construction - Sewers (Reel-folder 143.141)
    - Construction - Consultants - Campus Planning Consultant (Louis DeMonte), 1971 (Reel-folder 143.142)
  - Academic Planning and University Policies (Reel-folder 143.143)
  - Physical Plant - Construction - Buildings - Administrative Building (1 of 2), 1968 (Reel-folder 143.144)
  - Physical Plant - Construction - Building - Administration Building (2 of 2), 1968 (Reel-folder 144.144)
  - President's Office - Biennial Reports, 1948-1974 (Reel-folder 144.145)
  - President's Office - Personal - Speeches (Reel-folder 144.146)
  - President's Office - Public Relations - Robert W. MacVicar, 1971 (Reel-folder 144.147)
  - Administration
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 33 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Orders and Policies - Vending Machines (Reel-folder 144.148)
    - Orders and Policies - General (Reel-folder 144.149)
    - Patents - Battelle Development Corporation (Reel-folder 144.150)
    - Patents - Research Corporation (Reel-folder 144.151)
    - Patents - Policy Committee, 1968 (Reel-folder 144.152)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 33.01)
  - Promotion and Tenure - Worksheets, 1971 (Reel-folder 144.171)
  - Intergovernmental Coordinating Committee (Reel-folder 144.172)
  - Administration
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 34 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - President's Office - Dean of Faculty - Council of Deans, 1974 (Reel-folder 144.173)
    - Campus Events - State Government (Reel-folder 144.174)
    - Campus Events - State Government Day, 1970 (Reel-folder 144.175)
    - Campus Events - Twenty-Five Year Club, 1968 (Reel-folder 144.176)
    - Committees (Reel-folder 34.01)
    - Campus Events - General (Reel-folder 145.181)
    - Campus Events - Students - Faculty Conference, 1971 (Reel-folder 145.182)
    - Committees - Broadcast Media Committee, 1971 (Reel-folder 145.183)
    - Committees - Naming of Buildings Committee, 1967 (Reel-folder 145.184)
    - Committees - Campus Plan Committee, 1966 (Reel-folder 145.185)
    - Committees - Computer Committee, 1968 (Reel-folder 145.186)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 34.02)
    - Committees (Reel-folder 34.03)
    - Councils - Administrative Council, 1958 (Reel-folder 146.213)
    - Gifts and Grants - Research - Contracts Overhead Accounts (Reel-folder 146.214)
    - Orders and Policies (Reel-folder 34.04)
  - Research Centers and Institutes
    - Computer Center, 1971 (Reel-folder 147.222)
    - Environmental Fluid Dynamics Laboratory (Reel-folder 147.223)
    - Marine Science Center, 1972 (Reel-folder 147.224)
    - Radiation Center, 1971 (Reel-folder 147.225)
    - Sea Grant Colleges (Reel-folder 147.226)
    - X-Ray Science and Engineering Lab (Reel-folder 147.227)
  - Federal Extension - Service - Agriculture - General (Reel-folder 147.228)
  - Experiment Station - Agricultural - General, 1967 (Reel-folder 147.229)
  - Experiment Station - Agricultural - Closing of two Stations (Reel-folder 147.230)
  - Corvallis - Chamber of Commerce - Camp Adair (Reel-folder 147.231)
  - Colleges and Universities - Inaugurations - General, 1971 (Reel-folder 147.232)
  - Complaints - General [Sample only] (1 of 2), 1972 (Reel-folder 147.233)
  - Complaints - General [Sample only] (2 of 2), 1972 (Reel-folder 148.233)
  - Corvallis - Miscellaneous - Correspondence (Reel-folder 148.234)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1960 (Reel-folder 148.235)
  - Information, Inquiries, Requests, Etc. (Reel-folder 148.236)
  - Oregon State Employees Association, 1971 (Reel-folder 148.237)
  - Oregon State Departments - Executive Personnel Division, 1972 (Reel-folder 148.238)
  - General Information (Reel-folder 153.142)
  - Reference - Academic Achievement Report (Reel-folder 153.143)
  - Reference - Statistics - Baccalaureate and Commencement Speakers and Ministers (Reel-folder 153.144)
  - Reference - Miscellaneous Reports (Reel-folder 153.145)
  - Civil Service Salary Ranges, 1956-1959 (Reel-folder 153.146)
  - Civil Service, 1946 (Reel-folder 153.147)
  - Veteran's Administration Contracts, 1947-1948 (Reel-folder 153.148)
  - Reference File Reports - Miscellaneous
    - Education, US Office of - Annual Report OSU (Reel-folder 153.149)
    - Education, US Office of - Annual Report OSC (Reel-folder 154.149)
    - Science Development Plans OSC, 1967 (Reel-folder 154.150)
    - Building Program (Reel-folder 154.151)
    - Ten Year Building Program (Reel-folder 154.152)
    - Data Relative to Area of Various College Structures (Reel-folder 154.153)
  - Staff
    - Course Registration (Reel-folder 154.154)
    - Staff Registration Procedures (Reel-folder 154.155)
    - Staff Registration - Summer, 1970 (Reel-folder 154.156)
    - General (Reel-folder 154.157)
    - Correspondence - General, 1949-1966 (Reel-folder 154.158)
    - Salary Data (1 of 2), 1960-1967 (Reel-folder 154.159)
    - Salary Data (2 of 2), 1932-1960 (Reel-folder 154.160)
  - Reference File Reports - Miscellaneous - Library Transfer of Science Journal (Reel-folder 154.161)
  - Staff
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 38 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Organizations (Reel-folder 38.01)
    - Promotion and Tenure (Reel-folder 155.170)
    - Racial Discrimination in Fraternities and Sororities (Reel-folder 155.171)
    - Release of Staff Members (Reel-folder 155.172)
    - Retirement - General (Reel-folder 155.173)
    - Retirement - Lists (Reel-folder 155.174)
    - Retirement - Emeritus (Reel-folder 155.175)
    - Salary - Data (Reel-folder 155.176)
    - Salary - Differential, 1964-1966 (Reel-folder 155.177)
    - Statistics (Reel-folder 155.178)
    - Statistics - Class Enrollment (Reel-folder 155.179)
    - Statistics - Miscellaneous (Reel-folder 155.180)
    - Statistics - Service Reports (Reel-folder 155.181)
    - General - "Assistant In" Rank (Reel-folder 155.182)
    - Courtesy Appointments (Reel-folder 155.183)
    - Foreign Faculty (Reel-folder 155.184)
    - Graduate Assistants, Fellow, Etc. - General (Reel-folder 155.185)
    - General - Leaves without Salary (Reel-folder 155.186)
    - General - Release of Staff Members (Reel-folder 155.187)
  - Administration
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 39 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Campus Events (Reel-folder 39.01)
    - Committees (Reel-folder 39.02)
    - Councils (Reel-folder 39.03)
    - President's Office - Dean of Students - Black Student Union (Reel-folder 159.304)
    - Dean of Students (Reel-folder 39.04)
    - Dean of Undergraduate Students (Reel-folder 159.310)
    - Finance - Audits - State (Reel-folder 159.311)
    - Finance - Budgets - Biennial Reports (Reel-folder 159.312)
    - Finance - Budgets - Annual (1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Reel-folder 159.313)
    - Finance - Budgets - Annual (2 of 3), 1968-1969 (Reel-folder 159.314)
    - Finance - Budgets - Annual (3 of 3), 1969-1970 (Reel-folder 159.315)
    - Finance - Budget - Biennial Reports, 1969-1971 (Reel-folder 159.316)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 39.05)
    - Orders and Policies (Reel-folder 39.06)
    - Out of State Travel (Reel-folder 159.332)
    - Payment for Loss of Time of Appearance at Court (Reel-folder 159.333)
    - Personal Liability of Staff Members (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 159.334)
    - Personal Liability of Staff Members (Reel-folder 160.334)
    - Appearance of Political Speakers on OSU Campus (Reel-folder 160.335)
    - Publications - Printing (Reel-folder 160.336)
    - Scholarship Gifts - Scholarships (Reel-folder 160.337)
    - Short Course Authorization Policies (Reel-folder 160.338)
    - Smoking Regulations (Reel-folder 160.339)
    - Student Travel (Reel-folder 160.340)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 39.07)
    - Orders and Policies - Political Activities of Non-Classified Staff Members (Reel-folder 160.347)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 39.08)
  - Institutional Services
    - Civil Service Coordinator (Reel-folder 160.351)
    - Civil Service - General (Reel-folder 160.352)
    - Civil Service (Reel-folder 160.353)
    - Civil Service - Procedures - Overtime (Reel-folder 160.354)
    - Civil Service - Student Administrative Trainee Program - Summers (Reel-folder 160.355)
    - Fiscal Affairs - General (Reel-folder 160.356)
    - General - Department of Printing (Reel-folder 160.357)
    - General - Business Office - Value of Land, Buildings, and Inventory, 1951-1967 (Reel-folder 160.358)
    - General - News Bureau (Reel-folder 160.359)
    - General - Publications - Catalogue (Reel-folder 160.360)
    - General - Publications - Faculty Handbook (Reel-folder 160.361)
    - General - Publications - Promotional (Reel-folder 160.362)
    - General - Publications - Oregon Blue Book (Reel-folder 160.363)
    - Memorial Union - Activities and Programs (Reel-folder 160.364)
    - Registrar - Admission of High School Students on Accelerated Programs and Advanced Placement Programs (Reel-folder 160.365)
    - Registrar - Fee Remissions (Reel-folder 160.366)
    - Registrar - Schedule Clerk (Reel-folder 160.367)
    - General - Memorial Union - Managers Statements (Reel-folder 160.368)
  - Instruction
    Reel-Folder number added during data entry, as no number was assigned in container list.
    - Division (Reel-folder 41.01)
  - Physical Plant
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 42 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Administration - Physical Plant Director Position (Reel-folder 163.412)
    - Administration - Union Labor (Reel-folder 163.413)
    - Administration - General (Reel-folder 163.414)
    - Buildings (Reel-folder 42.01)
    - Construction (Reel-folder 42.02)
    - Departments (Reel-folder 42.03)
    - Physical Planning and Construction (Reel-folder 168.539)
    - Property - General (Reel-folder 168.540)
    - Leases - General (Reel-folder 168.541)
    - Property Purchases - General (Reel-folder 168.542)
    - Property - Rentals (Reel-folder 168.543)
    - General - Building Signs (Reel-folder 168.544)
    - General - Institutional Research - Electronic Data Processing (Reel-folder 168.545)
    - General - Institutional Research (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 168.546)
    - General - Institutional Research (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 169.546)
    - General (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 169.547)
    - General (2 of 2), 1965-1971 (Reel-folder 169.548)
    - General - Plant Rehabilitation (Reel-folder 169.549)
    - Buildings (Reel-folder 42.04)
    - General Rehabilitation Projects (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Reel-folder 169.558)
    - General Rehabilitation Projects (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Reel-folder 169.559)
    - Rehabilitation Program - General (Reel-folder 169.560)
    - General - Institutional Research (Reel-folder 169.561)
    - Land Purchases (Reel-folder 42.05)
    - Property - Sales - General (Reel-folder 169.565)
    - Property - Sales - General - CH2M Property Exchange (Reel-folder 169.566)
    - Property - Sales - Unowned Property in Campus Boundaries - Estimated Costs (Reel-folder 169.567)
    - Utilities - Camp Adair Incinerator (Reel-folder 169.568)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station and Federal Extension Service
    - Budget Deficits (Reel-folder 169.569)
    - Research - Cooperative Agreements; Alsea River Basin, USDI, State Dpt. of Interior and OSU Experiment Station (Reel-folder 169.570)
    - Research - Research and Marketing Funds (Reel-folder 169.571)
  - Experiment Stations
    - Agricultural (Reel-folder 44.01)
    - Engineering Experiment Stations (Reel-folder 170.591)
    - Engineering - Research - State Highway Projects (Reel-folder 170.592)
    - Engineering - Research - State Water Resources Board Agreement with OSU (Reel-folder 170.593)
    - Forest Research Division (Reel-folder 170.594)
    - Forest Experiment Station (Reel-folder 44.02)
  - Federal Extension Service
    - Agricultural (Reel-folder 45.01)
  - Research Centers and Institutes
    - Air Pollution Center (Reel-folder 171.608)
    - Behavioral Sciences, Center for Advanced Study (Reel-folder 171.609)
    - Center for Economic Education (Reel-folder 171.610)
    - Computer Center - Instructional Computer RQST (Reel-folder 171.611)
    - Computer Center (Reel-folder 171.612)
    - Malheur Environmental Field Station Consortium (Reel-folder 171.613)
    - Environmental Health Program (Reel-folder 171.614)
    - Environmental Health Science Center Newsletter (Reel-folder 171.615)
    - The Genetics Institute (Reel-folder 171.616)